<quotes>

<item>
   <quote>Every age has its storytelling form, and video gaming is a huge part of our culture. You can ignore or embrace video games and imbue them with the best artistic quality. People are enthralled with video games in the same way as other people love the cinema or theatre.</quote>
   <author>Andy Serkis</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Some people say video games rot your brain, but I think they work different muscles that maybe you don't normally use.</quote>
   <author>Ezra Koenig</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>The obvious objective of video games is to entertain people by surprising them with new experiences.</quote>
   <author>Shigeru Miyamoto</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I've learned over the years that if you start thinking about the race, it stresses you out a little bit. I just try to relax and think about video games...</quote>
   <author>Usain Bolt</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>That's really one of the things I love about video games. It's a whole new world every time you start.</quote>
   <author>Jennifer Hale</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Video games are a waste of time for men with nothing else to do. Real brains don't do that.</quote>
   <author>Ray Bradbury</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>As others have recently suggested, the term 'gamer' is no longer useful as an identity because games are for everyone [...] So I'll take a cue from my younger self and say I don't care about being a 'gamer,' but I sure do love video games.</quote>
   <author>Anita Sarkeesian</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>...we're in a new era right now. The idea that kids can play video games like Grand Theft Auto or any video game is amazing. The video games are one step before a whole other virtual universe.</quote>
   <author>Vin Diesel</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Playing video games is something I enjoy in my spare time. I'm a gamer, always have been.</quote>
   <author>Kevin Garnett</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>My mom didn't let me play video games growing up, so now I do. Gaming gives me a chance to just let go, blow somebody up and fight somebody from another dimension. It's all escapism.</quote>
   <author>Wayne Brady</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Video games are bad for you? That's what they said about rock-n-roll.</quote>
   <author>Shigeru Miyamoto</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>When I'm off the clock, I usually play video games - or do something nature-y so I can contribute to Mother Nature.</quote>
   <author>Harry Shum, Jr.</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>...I can't speak for every gamer out there, but I know when I play, I feel like I'm actually in the game. It's that intense.</quote>
   <author>Kevin Garnett</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>When I put out 'Video Games' in May 2011, it was a 5:25-minute love song; I was surprised when a lot of people said they were listening to it. I was surprised when it went to the radio, without me even knowing how something like that even happens!</quote>
   <author>Lana Del Rey</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>There was a naive quality in 1982 around technology and the start of video games. And that's like the start of electronic music - there was this statement and, ideologically, these things to fight for.</quote>
   <author>Thomas Bangalter</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm a huge video gamer, sometimes a little too much. I'll shut myself in my room just so I can play video games all day and I end up neglecting my friends.</quote>
   <author>Lucas Till</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm a huge video gamer, sometimes a little too much. I'll shut myself in my room just so I can play video games all day and I end up neglecting my friends.</quote>
   <author>Lucas Till</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I like video games, I like tech, I like being positive.</quote>
   <author>Jimmy Fallon</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>In college, before video games, we would amuse ourselves by posing programming exercises.</quote>
   <author>Ken Thompson</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I like video games, but they are very violent. I want to create a video game in which you have to help all the characters who have died in the other games. 'Hey, man, what are you playing?' 'Super Busy Hospital. Could you leave me alone? I'm performing surgery! This guy got shot in the head, like, 27 times!'</quote>
   <author>Demetri Martin</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>It seems astounding to me now that the video games are perhaps as important as the movie themselves. And people will spend 2 or 3 years obsessing about the video game in exactly the same way that they'd be obsessing about the movie if they were working on that.</quote>
   <author>John Cleese</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>It seems astounding to me now that the video games are perhaps as important as the movie themselves. And people will spend 2 or 3 years obsessing about the video game in exactly the same way that they'd be obsessing about the movie if they were working on that.</quote>
   <author>John Cleese</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Video games are ubiquitous now.</quote>
   <author>Eugene Jarvis</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>When I looked at the addictive qualities of video games and how they captivate people's attention, I decided to try the same technology for enhancing well-being.</quote>
   <author>Deepak Chopra</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I make funny videos of me playing video games, and I share those moments.</quote>
   <author>PewDiePie</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Zombies are always moving fast in video games. It makes sense if you think about it. Those games are all about hand-eye coordination and how quickly can you get them before they get you.</quote>
   <author>George A. Romero</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>There are plenty of skills I've learned from playing video games. It's more interactive than watching TV, because there are problems to solve as you're using your brain.</quote>
   <author>Shaun White</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I did spend much of my 20s sitting on a couch playing video games and ordering disgusting food.</quote>
   <author>John Gemberling</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Video games are so popular these days, getting the opportunity to star in one is something special. More people should do it.</quote>
   <author>Carrot Top</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Now, on nights that I can't sleep, I play video games alone until the morning.</quote>
   <author>Namie Amuro</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>This is You Don't Know Jack, I'm Cookie and you're... pathetic! Playing by yourself? Sheesh, go read a book or something!</quote>
   <author>Cookie Masterson</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>It's like I always say, Player One, it doesn't matter whether you win or lose as long as you get to play with yourself. Now get the hell away from the computer and go make some friends!</quote>
   <author>Cookie Masterson</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Hey, did you know that Carsey Werner attempted an actual [You Don't Know Jack] TV game show, with Paul Reubens hosting? It lasted six episodes on ABC before it got replaced. note  Well, at least the computer games aren't going anywhere...</quote>
   <author>Cookie Masterson</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Suppose I Can’t Believe It’s Not Butter came up with a &quot;5 stages of grief line&quot; of products. After I Can’t Believe It’s Not Butter, which product would come next in line? Answer: I’m Very Angry That It’s Not Butter</quote>
   <author>Cookie Masterson</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Many others will tell their children of Mario or Sonic or Master Chief. My hypothetical children will hear the tales of the great times I had with friends over intimate games of You Don't Know Jack.</quote>
   <author>Waltonky</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Honestly, to tell you the truth, being trapped in any video game sounds like a living nightmare to me. In most video games, the point is it's a fight for survival, so I think it would be a terrifying place to live.</quote>
   <author>John C. Reilly</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I guess I was a bit of a tomboy. I liked to catch frogs in the ditch, play soccer with my brother's friends and play video games.</quote>
   <author>Jud Tylor</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I love video games.</quote>
   <author>Chandler Riggs</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>While girls average a healthy five hours a week on video games, boys average 13. The problem? The brain chemistry of video games stimulates feel-good dopamine that builds motivation to win in a fantasy while starving the parts of the brain focused on real-world motivation.</quote>
   <author>Warren Farrell</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Scientists have shown that pigs are capable of playing simple video games, learning from each other, and even learning names.</quote>
   <author>Jane Velez-Mitchell</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>In video games and animation, you find that the toughest things to make different are the things that aren't words: grunts, groans, gasps.</quote>
   <author>Phil LaMarr</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>To make an embarrassing admission, I like video games. That's what got me into software engineering when I was a kid. I wanted to make money so I could buy a better computer to play better video games - nothing like saving the world.</quote>
   <author>Elon Musk</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Comics are a dying art. If you ask a little kid to choose between a video game with insane graphics or comic books... you have to compete with cable, satellite TV with its thousands of channels, and with video games that are like movies, with CGI explosions where you can blow up worlds.</quote>
   <author>Glenn Danzig</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Video games and computers have become babysitters for kids.</quote>
   <author>Taylor Kitsch</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm a total nerd. I love comic books and video games and most of all zombies!</quote>
   <author>Katie Leclerc</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Every new medium has, within a short time of its introduction, been condemned as a threat to young people. Pulp novels would destroy their morals, TV would wreck their eyesight, video games would make them violent.</quote>
   <author>Hanna Rosin</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Most of us grew up with video games in the household, either the original Nintendo in the living room or hoarding quarters for that trip to the arcade. And as time moves on, that line of nostalgia will keep moving forward where 'Frogger' gets replaced with 'Street Fighter 2' or 'Resident Evil 4.'</quote>
   <author>Rob Manuel</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>In the past, a lot of films based on video games think that the audience wants to experience what it's like to play the game, and that's absolutely not the case.</quote>
   <author>Duncan Jones</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>This generation is so dead. You ask a kid, 'What are you doing this Saturday?' and they'll be playing video games or watching cable, instead of building model cars or airplanes or doing something creative. Kids today never say, 'Man, I'm really into remote-controlled steamboats.'</quote>
   <author>Jack White</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I feel like maybe I'm part of that generation that became more of a gamer than a video consumer. It's always been something I've done with my spare time. If I had three hours on a Friday night, I'm not out partying. I'm probably playing video games.</quote>
   <author>Felicia Day</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>The only time I waste is time I spend doing something that, in my gut, I know I shouldn't. If I choose to spend time playing video games or sleeping in, then it's time well spent, because I chose to do it. I did it for a reason - to relax, to decompress or to feel good, and that was what I wanted to do.</quote>
   <author>Simon Sinek</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Video games are a special kind of play, but at root, they're about the same things as other games: embracing particular rules and restrictions in order to develop skills and experience rewards. When a game is well-designed, it's the balance between these factors that engages people on a fundamental level.</quote>
   <author>Tom Chatfield</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I love video games. I'm also slightly in awe of them. I'm in awe of their power in terms of imagination, in terms of technology, in terms of concept. But I think, above all, I'm in awe at their power to motivate, to compel us, to transfix us, like really nothing else we've ever invented has quite done before.</quote>
   <author>Tom Chatfield</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>When I'm making video games today, I want people to be entertained. I am always thinking, How are people going to enjoy playing the games we are making today? And as long as I can enjoy something other people can enjoy it, too.</quote>
   <author>Shigeru Miyamoto</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I do exercises on my Wii. It's nice to have games that keep you active. It's an excuse to play video games.</quote>
   <author>Jason Ritter</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>My place of refuge is definitely watching movies and playing video games. I know that's kind of hard to fathom.</quote>
   <author>Cam Newton</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>While films are a very visual and emotional artistic medium, video games take it one step further into the realm of a unique personal experience.</quote>
   <author>Jet Li</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I don't play video games because I know that if I ever started, I'd never be able to maintain a career again.</quote>
   <author>Jeff Lemire</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>The only other thing that's like video games for me is watching tennis on TV. I can have it on, and there's a rhythmic quality to it - I can be watching Wimbledon or the U.S. Open and still be working.</quote>
   <author>Lin-Manuel Miranda</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I find it a turnoff whenever men aren't into some kind of sport. And, no, video games don't count. I dated a guy who was into video games, and I wanted to shoot myself.</quote>
   <author>Eva Longoria</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Video games are engineered now, but the step I am trying to take, no one can engineer.</quote>
   <author>Bill Budge</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I think video games are a great kind of entertainment. They have replaced a lot of games people normally play with their friends and neighbours, like Monopoly.</quote>
   <author>Uwe Boll</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I've spent hours playing video games.</quote>
   <author>Harry Connick, Jr.</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I am a kid from the '70s, when video games first started coming out, so I definitely have to say I am a video game junkie to this day.</quote>
   <author>Cobi Jones</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I never play video games! I'm so bad at it. I have, like, no manual dexterity.</quote>
   <author>Kelly Hu</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I play a lot of ultra-violent video games.</quote>
   <author>Cory Monteith</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Ultimately, there's always been a link between comic books and video games, and comic books and movies, and then basically all three steadily becoming this sort of transmedia.</quote>
   <author>Troy Duffy</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm into video games, but only real specific lame video games.</quote>
   <author>Emily Browning</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Being young is an advantage. You've grown up with games as the dominant entertainment. You have a lot of experience of video games. So what do you want to see that's not been done? Innovation is really low cost for you. You can afford to take risks and fail to execute new ideas.</quote>
   <author>Kim Swift</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I love video games. When I was growing up, video games were very important to me.</quote>
   <author>Ben Schwartz</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Listen, I am such a nerd. I'm not one of those girls that goes, 'Ha, ha, hee, hee. I'm a nerd.' No, no, no - my brain mentality is the same as a 12-year-old little boy. The video games that I play, the things that I like to watch - I'm a Trekkie.</quote>
   <author>Mila Kunis</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I grew up nerdy, scrawny, playing video games, and getting picked on.</quote>
   <author>Josh Keaton</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>When I was growing up, I was an '80s baby, so I remember the Sega Genesis and the first Nintendo. I grew up in a time when we first started playing video games on a computer screen. Now there are headsets and your body's the controller.</quote>
   <author>Mehcad Brooks</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Probably the thing I use most in media is video games, but I have to limit myself. If I wake up super early in the morning, and I'm not tired, I'll play video games until everybody gets up.</quote>
   <author>Nolan Gould</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I think the thing we see is that as people are using video games more, they tend to watch passive TV a bit less. And so using the PC for the Internet, playing video games, is starting to cut into the rather unbelievable amount of time people spend watching TV.</quote>
   <author>Bill Gates</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>My experience with video games is a far cry from 'WWE 2K17.' Did I ever aspire to be that character? Man, I just wanted to be a hero to kids. Whether it's a character in a video game, a movie or a TV series, it's an accolade that I'm greatly appreciative of.</quote>
   <author>Bill Goldberg</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>There is evil prowling in the world - it shows up in our movies, video games and online fascinations, and finds its way into vulnerable hearts and minds.</quote>
   <author>Rick Perry</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>If I ever have downtime, I'm usually sitting in my place playing video games. Or eating sandwiches somewhere, or watching sports some place.</quote>
   <author>Hannibal Buress</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Sometimes we need to step back and understand the power of video games. 'Dear Esther' does just that. Through visuals, audio, and narration, this title weaves a story around the player as they explore different areas in the game.</quote>
   <author>Rob Manuel</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I see myself as a regular guy who likes playing video games with his nieces and nephews and poker with his family. I don't have an art collection or take exotic vacations. I enjoy being at home.</quote>
   <author>Vince Vaughn</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I used to play video games all the time, but now I don't because I don't have an attention span.</quote>
   <author>King Tuff</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Any real virtual reality enthusiast can look back at VR science fiction. It's not about playing games... 'The Matrix,' 'Snow Crash,' all this fiction was not about sitting in a room playing video games. It's about being in a parallel digital world that exists alongside our own, communicating with other people, playing with other people.</quote>
   <author>Palmer Luckey</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>There isn't quite a feeling you get from playing video games that you get when you're playing sports, which is like a sense of euphoria. You just get the satisfaction of doing something active and feeling good after.</quote>
   <author>Patrick Chan</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>The more downtime we have, the more time you have to play games like 'Ghost Recon Future Soldiers,' so for me it's a fun way to get integrated into video games and for me to have fun with my buddies and team up and go into battle with 'em, kind of like out there on court.</quote>
   <author>Kevin Love</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm pretty much an isolated person. I'd rather stay home and play video games.</quote>
   <author>Steve Jones</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Everything about video games has changed. The writing, the acting, the visuals, obviously - everything has gone to a new level.</quote>
   <author>Jennifer Hale</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I grew up with video games. My generation kind of grew up with the Nintendo and the Sega Genesis. Then, I had a Dreamcast and, finally, the PlayStation. So yeah, I've always been a big gamer.</quote>
   <author>CC Sabathia</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>When I started, people would come to interview me, and just knowing that I worked in videogames - it was like people wanted to stone me, it was that bad. People thought of video games as kind of a bad thing in society. Now, people that come to interview me, they have grown up with video games, and they know what they are; they've experienced it.</quote>
   <author>Yuji Horii</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Kids just don't read any more. They spend much more time with video games. It's just hard to get kids to read anything. Book sales have dropped dramatically, too. I think 90% of the books are bought only by 5% of the US population.</quote>
   <author>Stan Sakai</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I didn't play video games because my parents didn't allow it. That was banned from my childhood experience.</quote>
   <author>Kristin Kreuk</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I bought Justin Bieber's house... He had, like, this nook under the stairs which I didn't need, so I covered it up. When I ran into him, he was like 'What did you do with the nook? I used to go in there and play video games.' When I told him it was gone, he was so upset. I didn't think this 20-year-old boy would even care!</quote>
   <author>Khloe Kardashian</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I always have said from the beginning of my career that I was going for the 'Geek Trifecta' because I'm such a total geek. I want to be in everything that has to do with the things that I enjoyed when I was a kid, which was 'Battlestar Galactica,' and being in 'Big Bang Theory,' and being in video games.</quote>
   <author>Katee Sackhoff</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I can't play video games because I get too nervous. It just stresses me out.</quote>
   <author>Michael Cudlitz</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I really like baking, and I really like playing video games.</quote>
   <author>Rosanna Pansino</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Video games lend themselves completely to 3-D.</quote>
   <author>Howard Stringer</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I love playing video games, but I'm regularly disappointed in the limited and limiting ways women are represented.</quote>
   <author>Anita Sarkeesian</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Speaking as someone who's played a lot of video games, and at the end of the video game all you have is a memory, after woodworking you get this piece of furniture.</quote>
   <author>Thomas Middleditch</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I think video games are a huge part of our society now. Having kids play baseball video games helps them understand and love the game. It could actually push them to get out there and play the game for real. That's great for the sport.</quote>
   <author>Justin Verlander</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Sure, I like to win when I play basketball or board games or video games, but my day isn't ruined if I lose. I'm always up for a rematch. In all seriousness, that's something that's nice about maturing.</quote>
   <author>Aaron Staton</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>When I was 15, 16, 17 years old, I spent five hours a day juggling, and I probably spent six hours a day seriously listening to music. And if I were 16 now, I would put that time into playing video games.</quote>
   <author>Penn Jillette</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I think that as I had children, I have five sons, and they got into video games and were the prime ages through the development of video games. It was so much fun seeing them play the games and seeing it through their eyes.</quote>
   <author>John Lasseter</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I've always loved video games. I played 'Ms. Pac-man' with my dad, and I Ioved 'Galaga' and 'Tempest' and grew up on the standing arcade games. Even to this day, my dad will call me if he's playing 'Ms. Pac-man' and hold the phone up to the game.</quote>
   <author>Aisha Tyler</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I would love to make video games.</quote>
   <author>Spike Jonze</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Kids don't even read comic books anymore. They've got more important things to do - like video games.</quote>
   <author>Ang Lee</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I have friends who come to the Australia Zoo, and it's just, instead of playing video games, we get to hug and kiss a giraffe or walk a tiger.</quote>
   <author>Bindi Irwin</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I think, pretty much like everyone around my age, I grew up playing those classic video games. I wouldn't say I was addicted to them, but I definitely liked them.</quote>
   <author>Gene Luen Yang</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I love watching 'Orange Is the New Black,' and I play video games, like 'Call of Duty.'</quote>
   <author>Stipe Miocic</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>For the most part, I think video games do a good job of capturing the essence of boxing. However, I'd like to continue to see them push the realism, emphasizing the skill involved.</quote>
   <author>Sugar Ray Leonard</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>My first encounter with video games was pretty conventional. I was travelling with my parents - we used to take long cross country trips in the United States every summer - and we went into a restaurant where there happened to be a Pong machine, and I was... a lot of quarters went into that Pong machine, let's just say.</quote>
   <author>Warren Spector</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I started playing video games, and in 1978 I discovered Dungeons &amp; Dragons and started game-mastering and writing my own adventures and creating my own worlds.</quote>
   <author>Warren Spector</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I don't play video games.</quote>
   <author>Clive Owen</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Video games seem to be mostly a boy thing - viewed by young boys and created by big boys. I believe that if more videos games were created by women, the violence in these games - especially against women - would be rapidly toned down.</quote>
   <author>Madeleine M. Kunin</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Most video games, you build up toward the big, bad boss. And it's just a bigger, more powerful version of what you've been fighting all along in the game.</quote>
   <author>Jim Lee</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm really into video games.</quote>
   <author>Lucas Till</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I play a lot of video games, and I go to the gym.</quote>
   <author>Lucas Till</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm not even very good at most video games.</quote>
   <author>Freddie Wong</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I was a huge fan of video games; I wanted to write something, and I saw the tools at my fingertips to upload a video to my audience, and that's why I'm here today. I think that freedom and the lack of gatekeepers, combined with people's passion, is what really the true spirit of Internet geekdom is about.</quote>
   <author>Felicia Day</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I can't play video games or games on my phone because I'll go into a deep vortex, and no one will hear from me for weeks.</quote>
   <author>Nick Kroll</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>If I had a day to myself I would just play video games with my brothers.</quote>
   <author>Jeremy Lin</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I think a punt can be a big play in a game. If it's anything like a real game, then you realize that a Pat McAfee punt that downs someone inside the 2-yard line can really swing a game. I'm all for punting in video games.</quote>
   <author>Andrew Luck</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>There are big lines between those who play video games and those who do not. For those who don't, video games are irrelevant. They think all video games must be too difficult.</quote>
   <author>Shigeru Miyamoto</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>If you are willing to take the trip through 'Analogue,' you'll be rewarded with some of the best writing in gaming today and a look into the future of what kind of meaningful stories video games are capable of telling.</quote>
   <author>Rob Manuel</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>When I was a child, there really weren't very many video games, but I do have memories of 'Pong.' Maybe it was 'Pong.' It was a home system in Japan, so maybe it wasn't the real 'Pong.' It was just sort of a Japanese game that was similar to 'Pong.'</quote>
   <author>Hideo Kojima</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I have been listening a lot to The Carpenters and Neil Diamond, Elton John, and thinking, like, 'God, it'd be great to write a sort of subversive, alternative ballad,' like Lou Reed does so well with 'Perfect Day.' And I really loved 'Video Games' - at the time, it hadn't really got as big, but it's a classic song; you can't deny it.</quote>
   <author>Bat for Lashes</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm part of that original generation that came up playing video games, that pumped a lot of our allowance into video games. We financed the rise of video games. I started playing them in the Straw Hat Pizza Palace at the Carriage Square Mall in Oxnard, CA.</quote>
   <author>Rich Moore</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I think it would be impossible to make a movie about video games if there wasn't some violence that we know from video games.</quote>
   <author>Rich Moore</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>It feels like there's something for everyone in video games. It's not just a toy for a certain age group. It's steeped in the culture now.</quote>
   <author>Rich Moore</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>My manager introduced me to the 'Rise to Honor' team. I was curious about what it took to be involved in video games, a completely new form of entertainment to me.</quote>
   <author>Jet Li</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I have an older brother and older sister. My older sister is the girliest girl on the planet, so I just hated everything about that. I did anything my brother did. He actually got me into wrestling. I watched it because he did, and I played video games because he did.</quote>
   <author>AJ Lee</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I like to play video games like 'Rock Band' and 'Guitar Hero.'</quote>
   <author>Carmen Electra</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I've been playing hand-held video games since 1995. Its my way of training my brain.</quote>
   <author>Marilyn Minter</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Video games as a storytelling medium are, from a mathematical standpoint, a branching narrative. You start at one place, you can go in multiple different directions, and there's a multitude of different endings.</quote>
   <author>Chris Milk</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>My brother and I have always had this theory that, as stupid as it sounds, in video games, there is a certain hand-eye coordination and a thought process that you can learn.</quote>
   <author>Landon Donovan</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I grew up playing video games. And the cool thing about the EA Sports games is they took me through the whole motion-capture thing, where they put little sensors on my body so the video game really is me. It actually moves the way I move.</quote>
   <author>Landon Donovan</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>In the time between records, I always have lots of stuff going on. I shoot photography, make little sculptures, play video games.</quote>
   <author>Adam Jones</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm geeky about video games. I don't stay inside a lot and just play them 24/7, but if I had the chance, I probably would.</quote>
   <author>Kodi Smit-McPhee</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I have been playing video games since the Atari 2600 days.</quote>
   <author>Burnie Burns</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm an old guy, so I started out playing 'Pong' with my brothers, and 'Mario Bros.' and whatnot. But we really got involved and got intense when 'Tecmo Super Bowl' came out. That's when we really started playing video games, and it got intense.</quote>
   <author>Kevin Dillon</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I like to play video games and read.</quote>
   <author>Richard Sherman</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Once we start seeing video games that have more memorable characters, you'll see better movie adaptations.</quote>
   <author>David S. Goyer</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm that girl that's a hardcore musician and loves to sing and write and play instruments but, at the same time, loves video games, metal music, and just being a goofy person.</quote>
   <author>Christina Grimmie</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>The modern video games kind of - they're too three dimensional.</quote>
   <author>Dan Auerbach</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I am terrible at video games and I am really competitive. And if I am not the best at something, I go absolutely crazy!</quote>
   <author>Gemma Arterton</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I've been a video game guy since I was eight years old and got my first Nintendo. I've been addicted to video games ever since.</quote>
   <author>A.J. Styles</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I got addicted to Tetris, playing it in my basement, I was missing all these airplane flights over it. After the fourth one that I missed, I realized I needed to get rid of this thing - so ever since then, I don't play video games any more.</quote>
   <author>Bam Margera</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I love video games. I love, love, love them! I also love 'Star Wars.' I wish Jedi was a true religion.</quote>
   <author>Kunal Nayyar</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I played mostly games like Asteroids and Pac-Man. Today, when I go into an arcade, the games are much more difficult and complex. I don't think I could even play some of the video games that are out there today.</quote>
   <author>Brandi Chastain</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Sport-based video games occupy an odd space within the sphere of modern home entertainment. Reliably enjoyed by millions, the sport-based video game stands at what sometimes feels like an oblique angle from the larger medium, and in ways that can be hard to articulate.</quote>
   <author>Tom Bissell</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>All video games are games, obviously. They're designed. They're digital. They have rules; they give an audience some type of vicarious experience.</quote>
   <author>Tom Bissell</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I would say I'm pretty much the exact same as the stereotypical American kid. I mean I'm really lazy, I play a lot of video games, I like girls. I like, you know, the violence and action type thing.</quote>
   <author>Callan McAuliffe</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I do love video games. But after a while, you feel like you really need to get up and do something.</quote>
   <author>Patrick Chan</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Getting inside the mind of a terrorist wasn't difficult at all. Even as children, human beings fabricate elaborate revenge fantasies. We're not a particular species. Check out popular video games.</quote>
   <author>Alan Dean Foster</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm a huge nerd, I admit to that. I love to play video games, I love to read, and of course, I've gotta still get my studies in and all. I love to learn. But I also love to do stop motion animation with my little Lego figures. I love to play around on the computer with that.</quote>
   <author>Atticus Shaffer</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Before I was on 'Idol,' I just sat at home and played video games all day long. Now I get to travel and work towards my dream. It's the best feeling ever.</quote>
   <author>Jessica Sanchez</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>The 1980s was a time of the great recession of interactive entertainment. When Atari fell in 1982, until Nintendo launched its console, video games were an outcast for five years.</quote>
   <author>Bing Gordon</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>It's very difficult for people who don't play video games to understand their power simply by watching, and it's very difficult for people who aren't close to technology to understand how rapidly it can change whatever it touches.</quote>
   <author>Bing Gordon</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm a huge 'Call of Duty' fan, 'Minecraft' and all those kinds of video games. I'm constantly playing video games every day.</quote>
   <author>Olivia Holt</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>We turn off the TV, video games and computer - except for homework - during the week. The TV's reserved for Friday night, Saturday and Sunday just because that's the time to do homework, and it makes it that much less chaotic in our house.</quote>
   <author>Candace Cameron Bure</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>My older brother Billy was really into video games, and of course I followed suit. I was such a dork - I was so geeky!</quote>
   <author>Ciara Renee</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm such a video game fan that being able to do voices in video games is just fantastic.</quote>
   <author>Will Friedle</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Since young people would much rather play fast-action, rapidly advancing video games, and gambling laws for slot machines and roulette tables haven't changed much since the 1950s, look for casinos to build large video game tournament centers and allow people to bet on the action, similar to betting on college basketball.</quote>
   <author>Thomas Frey</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I'm not really big on video games at all, I played a lot at the arcade as a kid. I didn't have a system growing up at my house.</quote>
   <author>Kyp Malone</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I miss video games where the jump-kick was the trickiest combo to master.</quote>
   <author>Jay Asher</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>When I finish my school work for the day, I like to go play basketball, ride my bike or skateboard, play video games, or go free running.</quote>
   <author>Max Charles</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Video games are a huge, incredibly popular, world-transforming medium.</quote>
   <author>Austin Grossman</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>To me the arcade experience is the ultimate gaming experience.</quote>
   <author>Eugene Jarvis</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I've watched with a kind of wary eye how gaming has progressed. I was there at the beginning with Pong in the arcade, and a lot of my great childhood memories were around a 'Tempest' machine.</quote>
   <author>Trent Reznor</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>When I put a quarter into an arcade machine or call up an emulated game on my computer, I do it to escape the world that is a slave to the time that makes things fall apart. I have never played these games to occupy my world.</quote>
   <author>D. B. Weiss</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>When I walk into a video arcade filled with 16- or 17-year-old boys, I may as well be Marilyn Monroe.</quote>
   <author>Jennifer Coolidge</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I restore vintage Atari XY arcade video game machines.</quote>
   <author>Roger Avary</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>When I was young, I was on a real hot streak with 'Crazy Climber.' There was a good three-week span where I couldn't get that game out of my head. I could not get back to the arcade fast enough to try and climb up there and not get kicked by a potted plant this time. That one got under my skin.</quote>
   <author>Rich Moore</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>My favorite video game of all time is called 'Black Tiger'. It's a Capcom Dungeons and Dragons game from 1987. I have the actual arcade version sitting in my office.</quote>
   <author>Ernest Cline</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>The gaming world is a complete mystery to me! Well, I did play Pac Man and Frogger using big machines at an arcade back in the '80s.</quote>
   <author>Doug Jones</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I still have my old Nintendo 64 that works. And I hook it up, and I still play the original 'Goldeneye.' I'm that geek. I have an 'NBA Jam' arcade machine in my office at 'SNL.'</quote>
   <author>Taran Killam</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I do Dance Dance Revolution. I'm not as good as the little kids that come in the arcade. Their little feet go crazy fast. I'm not that fast, but I'm good on it!</quote>
   <author>Missy Elliott</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>When I was a kid, I had an Atari 2600, and I would play Pac Man, Frogger, all that kind of stuff. And I did enjoy going to the arcade.</quote>
   <author>Jack McBrayer</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>When I was growing up, I did go to the arcade. We had a neighborhood arcade, and my friends and I would go fairly regularly.</quote>
   <author>Gene Luen Yang</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>That's one thing I love about my son - he's just a gamer at heart, he loves everything. He'll still play 'Pole Position,' or just old things at an arcade. He just loves games. He's not a graphics snob at all. I love him.</quote>
   <author>Ron Funches</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I remember the first Mortal Kombat, when that came out, that was the hardest game of all time. There would be lines at the arcade around the block, and I still love all of the Mortal Kombat games.</quote>
   <author>Diego Corrales</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I actually have the Arcade PC at home, and it has 5,500 games on it. Everything from the old school, Galaga, Tron, Missile Command, anything you can think of, they're all on there. I love the old school games.</quote>
   <author>Diego Corrales</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>You can't kill Q-Bert! You gotta talk to it, get to know it better. Then kill it!</quote>
   <author>Sam Brenner - Pixels</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>The real classics. Defender. Pac-man. Astroids. Games you play in an arcade which was a building outside of your house. You would go there with your friends, listen to music, cute girls everywhere. In ancient times, they call it 'socializing'.</quote>
   <author>Sam Brenner - Pixels</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>What am I looking at right now? Are you guys, soldiers or the casts of Magic Mike? Are you gonna fight or dance naked?</quote>
   <author>Ludlow Lamonsoff - Pixels</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Pac-Man's always been faster than the ghost.</quote>
   <author>Eddie Plant - Pixels</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I don't know WHY I'm telling you this... You didn't even listen last time!</quote>
   <author>Cranky Kong - Donkey Kong Country</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>For just 3 coins, I'll let you play with my instrument anytime you want.</quote>
   <author>Candy Kong - Donkey Kong 64</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>Gimme some slack, Donkey-dude! I'm all cleaned out!</quote>
   <author>Funky Kong - Donkey Kong 64</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>I've been waiting a long time for this moment. Soon, Donkey Kong and his pretty little island will be no more!</quote>
   <author>King K. Rool - Donkey Kong 64</author>
</item>

<item>
   <quote>If Pac-Man had affected us as kids, we'd all be running around in dark rooms, munching pills and listening to repetitive electronic music.</quote>
   <author>Marcus Brigstocke</author>
</item>

</quotes>